Stretch your hand forward. Father we thank you.
Holy Ghost,we thank you.
Your body is temple of the Holy Ghost.
My body is the temple of the Holy Ghost.
Right now open your lips and if there is any barrier...
whatever that unclean spirit might have used
to connect you with himself,
Right now begin to break that spirit
in the name of Jesus Christ.
Break that spirit right now.
Your body is a temple of the Holy Ghost.
Begin to break the spirit in the name of Jesus.
Break it! Open your lips right now
Begin...begin...begin...begin...In the name of Jesus.
In the name of Jesus
Break the spirit!
Open your lips...open your lips
Whatever spirit that is tormenting your life.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Listen to me once again.
Whatever spirit that stands against you,
that connects you to failure,
that connects you to disease,
that connects you to set back,
that connect you to hardship,
that connects you to nightmares,
Open your lips and begin to break that spirit right now.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
You evil spirit...out
say ..."out!"
In the mighty name of Jesus
Say, "my body is a temple of the Holy Ghost."
Say, " out!"
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ.
Open your lips and begin to disconnect yourself.
Disconnect yourself.
Say, "Holy Ghost Fire."
Manifestation of evil spirits
You evil spirit....out!
Right now begin to loose it!
Kick it...kick it out. Kick it out of your life.
Kick it out in the name of Jesus.
Say you evil spirit,
"in my business, in my life,
in my career.....say out!'
Kick it out!
Kick it out, in Jesus name!
You evil spirit...in my life,
in my business, in my career.
Say I kick you out.
Go!
Fiery Mass prayer with Prophet T.B Joshua.
Open your lips!
Kick it out!
Holy Ghost!
Kick it out, kick it out, in the name of Jesus!
Begin to kick it out, in your life!
Fiery Mass prayer with Prophet T.B Joshua.
Viewers all over the world, those of you who are under the influence of this telecast.
Right now, begin to kick it out!
Kick him out
Kick satan out!
Kick the demon out!
Kick him out!
Kick him out...in the name of Jesus.
Viewers all over the world, in the mighty name of Jesus.
Kick it out!
Kick that demon out! In your system... kick it out!
In your home...kick him out.
In the name of Jesus, kick him out.. kick him out...kick him out!
In the name of Jesus
Viewers all over the world, where can you go from his presence?
Anywhere you are, whatever spirit is tormenting your life.
Whatever spirit is connecting you to himself...
be broken...be broken...in the name of Jesus.
I command that spirit.
Your body is the temple of the Holy Ghost.
Viewers all over the world, whatever spirit that is tormenting your life...tormenting your career.
In the name of Jesus...out!
Fiery Mass prayer with Prophet T.B Joshua.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ
Those of you who are under the sound of this telecast, give thanks to God.
Give thanks to him. The Lord is good.
Give thanks to God for your liberty.
We believe that you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today
and stay up to date with the latest: prophecies,deliverances, service and testimonies
from the SCOAN. Emmanuel TV.
Changing lives, changing nations and changing the world.